air.io 2019-07-08

# 

                                          PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy explains how Conception Mark LP (brand name – AIR, Agency of Internet Rights,
hereinafter – “we”, “our”, “us”) use and storage any personal data we collect about you, when you use
our web-site and services.
Conception Mark LP as a data controller process your personal data in accordance with the General Data
Protection Regulation (GDPR).
    1. What personal data we collect about you
        We collect your personal data when you register on this web-site, create personal account,
        conclude the Agreement on our web-site (hereinafter – “Agreement”):
        - Name, surname, gender, date of birth, photo
        - Country, address
        - Phone, email, Skype, Viber, WhatsApp
        - Web-page, web-page in social media
        - Google Account, Google Plus
        - Bank details
        - Cookies
        - IP addresses.
    2. Cookies
        Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and
        visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to
        compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org
        or www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above
        websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.
    3. Why we collect your personal data
        We collect your personal data in order to:
        - conclude the Agreement with you and fulfill it
        - create and operate your personal account on this web-site
        - administer promote and monetize your content on YouTube and other agreed platforms and
             provide them with your personal data for this purpose
        - provide you information about our services, products, news and proposals
        - send you reports according to the Agreement
        - send money to your payment details
        - inform you about the services provided to you
        - contact with you if necessary
        Our lawful reason for processing your personal data is your consent and the Agreement, in order
        we could provide you the services under the Agreement and fulfill our obligations (contractual
        necessity).
    4. What we do with your personal data
        Your personal data is stored on the server of data processor, located in Germany, and on the
        servers of the cloud-based service of data processor. Our data processors process your personal
        data under the appropriate agreements with us and in accordance with the standards of the

   General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). For more information on where your personal data is
   stored, please contact us at support@air.io.
   For providing our content administration services to you we pass your personal data to YouTube,
   banks and other financial institutions, which we use for sending money to your payment details,
   and also our affiliated or associated companies, partner-companies for the purposes of providing
   the services to you on our behalf.
   We will not sell or distribute your personal data to another third parties unless we have your
   permission or required by law to do so.
5. Transferring your information outside of Europe
   When we provide our services to you, the personal data which you give to us may be transferred
   to countries outside the European Union: to the banks and other financial institutions, which we
   use for sending money to your payment details, affiliated or associated companies, partner-
   companies. Where this is the case we will take steps to make sure the right security measures are
   taken so that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this policy. By submitting
   your personal data, you’re agreeing to this transfer, storing or processing.
6. Marketing
   We would like to send you information about our services, products, offers, updates etc. which
   may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive such information, you may opt out at
   any point to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes, by sending e-mail to the address:
   support@air.io.
7. How long we keep your personal data
   We keep your personal data during the whole term of Agreement and after its termination -before
   the date you notify us that you wish us delete your personal data.
8. What are your rights
   - Access to your personal data
       You may request a copy of the information that we hold about you by sending e-mail to
       support@air.io. We will respond to your request within one month of receipt of the request.
       We want your personal data to be accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or
       remove personal data you think is inaccurate by sending e-mail to support@air.io.
   - Objections to processing of personal data
       You may lodge an objection to the processing of your personal data by sending e-mail to
       support@air.io.
   - Data Portability
       You have a right to receive the personal data which you have given to us, in a structured,
       commonly used and machine-readable format and transmit the data to third party from us by
       sending a request to e-mail address support@air.io.
   - Right to be Forgotten
       If you wish to completely delete all your personal data that we hold, you should send a request
       to e-mail support@air.io. But we can do it only if the Agreement is terminated with you.
   - Right to refuse from receiving the information
       You can inform us about the reluctance of further receiving any marketing information from
       us by sending a request to the e-mail address support@air.io. If the Agreement is not
       terminated with you, we will still continue to send you the reports and necessary information
       in order to fulfill our obligations under the Agreement.
9. What we do to secure your personal data

    We are committed to ensuring that your personal data is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized
    access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures
    to safeguard and secure the information we get from you.
10. Complaints
    If you suppose that your personal data has been processed in a way that does not meet the GDPR,
    you have a specific right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority in the UK – the
    Information Commissioner’s Office.
11. Changes to our privacy policy
    We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web
    page. This privacy policy was last updated on 24 May 2018.
12. How to contact us
    Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or personal data we hold
    about you:
    - Address: 39/5 Granton Crescent, Edinburgh, EH51BN, United Kingdom
    - Email: support@air.io
